Guide to the Veranus A. Moore Papers, 1836-1958
Moore, Veranus A. papers, 1836-1958
- Series VIII. Photographs
  - Miscellaneous Family and Friends - Negatives (Box 43, Folder 5)
_______ and Frederick Willan Wood. " Simultaneous method of inoculating cattle and carabaos with serum from animals that have been recently immunized." Reprinted from The Philippine Journal of Science, February 1914.
Way, Cassius. "Practical application of the agglutination method for the diagnosis of glanders." American Veterinary Review, September 1907.
Wedderburn, Alex J. "Report on the extent and character of food and drug adulteration." U. S. Department of Agriculture, Division of Chemistry, Bulletin No. 41, 1894.
Wehr, Everett E. "Description of a new genus and species of nematode worm occurring in the northwestern belted kingfisher, with a key to the genera of the subfamily acuariinae." Reprinted from the Proceedings of the United States National Museum, 1931.
_______. "A new specied of nematode worm from the sage grouse." Reprinted from the Proceedings of the United States National Museum, 1931.
Weiser, Stephen. "Die melasse-futterung." VIII Congres International de Medecine Veterinaire, Budapest, 1905.
Weissenberg, Richard. "Flub und bachneunauge (lampetra fluviatillis l. und lampetra planeri bloch), ein morphologisch-biologischer vergleich." Reprinted from Zoolog. Anzeiger, 17 June 1925.
Welch, William H. "Adaptation in pathological processes." Reprinted from Science, 28 May 1897.
_______. "Preliminary report of investigations concerning the causation of hog cholera." Reprinted from The Johns Hopkins Hospital Bulletin, December 1889.
_______. "Bacteriological investigations of diptheria in the United States." Reprinted from The American Journal of the Medical Sciences, October 1894.
Wesbrook, F. F. "Beitrag zur immunisirungsfrage." Reprinted from Hygienischen Rundschau, 1894.
Whipple, George C. "The water supplies of the New York metropolitan district with special reference to their purification." Reprinted from Journal of the New Englad Water Works Association, 1905.
Whitaker, George M. "The milk supply of Boston and other New Englad cities." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Burean of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 20, 1898.
White, G. F. and W. E. Dove. "The causation of creeping eruption." Reprinted from The Journal of the American Medical Association, 26 May 1928.
White, William Charles. "Natural and artificial cure of tuberculosis." National Tuberculosis Association, Technical Series No. 1, 1925.
Wilder, Burt Green. "American reports upon anatomical nomenclature, 1889-1890. Cornell publication? 5 February 1892.
_______. "Brain-weight, etc." Reprinted from "The gross anatomy of the brain" in Wood's Reference Handbook of the Medical Sciences, n.d.
_______. "The desirability and the feasibility on the acquisition of some real and accurate knowledge of the brain by pre-collegiate scholars." Reprinted from Science, 17 December 1897.
_______."The dorsal sack, the aulix and the diencephalic flexure." Abstract of address read before the American Neurological Association, 4 June 1896.
_______. "Fissural diagrams." Cornell publication, December 1891.
_______. "The fundamental principles of anatomical nomenclature." Reprinted from The Medical News, 19 December 1891.
_______. "The morphological importance of the membranous or other thin portions of the parieties of the encephalic cavities." Reprinted from The Journal of Comparative Neurology, October 1891.
_______. "Neural Terms." Reprinted from The Journal of Comparative Neurology, February 1897.
_______. "The paroccipital fissure: should it be recognized and so designated?" Reprinted from Proceedings of the Association of American Anatomists, December 1895.
_______. "Revised interpretation of the central fissures of the educated suicide's brain exhibited to the Association in 1894." Reprinted from the Jounral of Nervous and Mental Disease, October 1900.
_______. "Some misapprehensions as to the simplified nomenclature of anatomy.´Address of the President of the Association of American Anatomists, 28 December 1898.
_______. "What is the morphologic status of the olfactory portion of the brain." Abstract of address given before the American Society of Naturalists, 29 December 1897.
Wiley, H. W. "Foods and food adulterants." U.S. Department of Agirculture, Division of Chemistry, Bulletin No. 13, 1893.
Williams, Walter Long. "Contagious abortion in cattle." Reprinted from the Annual Report of the New York Veterinary College for the Year 1913-1914, 1915.
Williamson, F.P. and F.E. Emery. "Tuberculosis and its prevention." North Carolina Agricultural Experiment Station, Bulletin No. 117, 28 June 1895.
Wills, John Gordon. "The retest of reacting cattle." Reprinted from the 22nd Annual Report of the U.S. Live Stock Sanitary Association, 1918.
Wilson, H.V. "Formation of the blastopoer in the frog egg." Reprinted from Anatomischer Anzeiger, 1900.
_______. "Marine biology at Beaufort." Reprinted from The American Naturalist, 1900.
_______. "Notes on a species of pelomyxa. Reprinted from The American Naturalist, 1900.
Woods, Charles D. "Poultry investigations at the Maine Agricultural Experiment Station." U.S. Department of Agirculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 90, 1906.
Wright, Jonathan. "The origin and heredity of matter." Reprinted from the St Louis Medical Review, August-September, 1906.
Y
Yard, W. W. "Hog cholera and its control." State of Colorado Bulletin No. 1, ca. 1918.
Miscellaneous New York State Department of Health Publications
"Annual report of the Division of Laboratories and Research." Extract from Fiftieth Annual Report of the State Department of Health for 1929, 1930.
"Cancer: facts which every adult should know." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 20, 1919.
"The conduct of an isolation period for communicable disease in a home." New York State Department of Health, 1919.
"Diphtheria." New York State Department of Health, Division of Communicable Diseases, n.d. "Diphtheria: information for parents, physicians and health officers." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 23, 1919.
"The Division of Laboratories and Research: A short account of its history and present status." New York State Department of Health, n.d.
"Extract from twenty-ninth annual report." New York State Department of Health, 1908.
"Laboratories approved for public health service." New York State Department of Health, 1930.
"Measles." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 17, 1919.
"Measles and whooping cough." New York State Department of Health, Division of Communicable Diseases, n.d.
"poliomyelitis, acute anterior: information for parents, physicians and health officers." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 25, 1920.
"Scarlet fever." New York State Department of Health, Division of Communicable Diseases, n.d.
"Scarlet fever-scarlatina: information for parents, physicians and health officers." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 15, 1921.
"Smallpox." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 11, 1919.
"Statement in regard to state aid for count and municipal laboratories." New York State Department of Health, February 1924.
"Typhoid fever: information for patients, physicians and health officers." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 16, 1919.
"Vaccination: what it is, what it does, what its claims are on the people." New York State Department of Health, 1908
"Vaccination." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 12, 1919.
"Venereal diseases." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 26, 1917.
"Whooping cough: information for parents, physicians and health officers." New York State Department of Health, Circular No. 18, 1919.
Health News, New York State Department of Health, 5 August 1929.
Health News, New York State Department of Health, 21 October 1929.
Health News, New York State Department of Health, 14 July 1930.
Health News, New York State Department of Health, 23 February 1931.
Miscellaneous New York State Department of Farms and Markets Publications
"Article 5 of the agricultural law chapter 1 of the consolidated laws relating to diseases of domestic animals." Reprinted from New York State Department of Agriculture Bulletin No. 11, 1909.
"The foot and mouth disease in New York State." State of New York, Department of Agriculture, n.d..
"A partial list of owners of pure-bred live stock in New York State." State of New York, Department of Agriculture, Bulletin No. 17, 1910.
"Provisions of article IV of the agricultural law relating to diseases of domestic animals." State of New York, Department of Agriculture, 1908.
"Rabies." State of New York, Department of Agriculture, 24 October 1908.
"Report of the Commission for the Investigation of Bovine Tuberculosis," New York State Commission for the Investigation of Bovine Tuberculosis, March 1915.
"Stallion enrollments for the year ending December 31, 1917." State of New York, Department of Farms and Markets, Circular No. 165, 1917.
"Summary report of farm bureau work in New York State for the calendar year 1914." Farm Bureaus of New York, Bulletin No. 6, June 1915.
Miscellaneous United States Department of Agriculture Publications
"The control of bovine tuberculosis." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry ,Circular 175, 1911.
"Control and eradication of tuberculosis in cattle." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, List No. 1, 1 July 1918.
"Crossing improved breeds of swine with the common hogs of Florida." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Circular No. 4, 1895.
"Directions for use of blackleg vaccine." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Circular No. 21, 1897.
"Directory of the Bureau of Animal Industry." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, 1913.
"Eleven miscellaneous papers on animal parisites." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 35, 1902.
"How to distinguish the different mosquitoes of North America." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Division of Entomology, Circular No. 40, 1900.
"How to select good cheese." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Circular No. 11, n.d.
"Investigations concerning bovine tuberculosis." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry Bulletin No. 7, 1894.
"Milk as food." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Farmers' Bulletin No. 74, 1908.
"Mycotic stomatitis of cattle." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Circular No. 51, 1904.
"Proceedings of a conference of federal and state representatives to consider plans for the eradication of the cattle tick." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Bulletin No. 97, 1907.
"Regulations concerning cattle transportation." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Order No. 8, 1897.
"Regulations governing entrance to the veterinary inspector examination." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Circular No. 150, 1909.
"Regulations governing the interstate movement of live stock." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Order No. 263, 1919
"Regulations governing the meat inspection of the United States Department of Agriculture. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Order No. 137, 1906
"Regulations governing the meat inspection of the United States Department of Agriculture. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Order No. 150, 1908
"Regulations governing the meat inspection of the United States Department of Agriculture. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Order No. 211, 1914
"Regulations governing the meat inspection of the United States Department of Agriculture. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, Order No. 211, revised, 1922.
Reports of experiments with various insecticide substances, chiefly upon insects affecting garden crops, made under the direction of the entomologist." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Division of Entomology, Bulletin No. 11, 1886.
"Service Announcements." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, No. 30, 1909.
"Special report on the market for American horses in foreign countries." U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1898.
"State sanitary requirements governing admission of live stock." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry, 1911.
"Tuberculosis: A plain statement of facts regarding the disease, prepared especially for farmers and others interested in live stock." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Farmers' Bulletin No. 473, 1916.
"Tuberculosis in live stock: Detection, control and eradication." U.S. Department of Agriculture, Farmers' Bulletin No. 1069, 1919.
Miscellaneous United States Department of Public Health Publications
Municipal ordinances, rules and regulations pertaining to public hygiene." United States Treasury Department, Public Health and Marine-Hospital Service, Public Health Report No. 70, 1912
Public Health Reports, Volume 26, No. 14 (7 April 1911)
"Report of commission of medical officers detailed by authority of the President to investigate the cause of yellow fever." United States Treasury Department, Marine-Hospital Service, 1899.
"Yellow fever: its nature, diagnosis, treatment, and prophylaxis and quarantine regulations relating thereto." United States Treasury Department, Marine-Hospital Service, 1899.
Venereal disease information. United States Treasury Department, Public Health Service, Vol 12, no. 10 (20 October 1931).
Miscellaneous
United States Bureau of the Census. "Tuberculosis in the United States [ prepared for the International Congress on Tuberculosis, Washington, Fall 1908]. Census Publications on Mortality Statistics, V.S. pamphlet No. 109, ca. 1909.
A number of complete journals were also discarded
American Journal of Pathology
Vol. 1, no. 5 (Sept 1925)
American Medical Association Bulletin
Vol. 25, no. 4 (April 1930)
Vol. 26, no. 10 (Oct 1931)
Centralblatt für Bakteriologie, Parasitenkunde und Infektionskrankheiten
Vol. 31, no. 6 (Feb 1902)
Vol. 31, no. 9 (Mar 1902)
Vol. 31, no. 21/22 (Jul 1902)
Vol. 31, no. 25 (Jul 1902)
Vol. 31, no. 26 (Aug 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 2 (Aug 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 5 (Sep 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 10 (Oct 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 11 (Oct 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 14 (Nov 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 16 (Dec 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 17 (Dec 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 18 (Dec 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 20 (Dec 1902)
Vol. 32, no. 21 (Feb 1903)
Journal of the American Medical Association
Vol. 83, no.3 (19 Jul 1924)
Vol. 83, no.4 (26 Jul 1924)
Vol. 83, no.6 (9 Aug 1924)
Vol. 83, no.7 (16 Aug 1924)
Vol. 83, no.8 (23 Aug 1924)
Vol. 83, no.9 (30 Aug 1924)
Vol. 83, no.10 (6 Sep 1924)
Vol. 93, no.12 (21 Sept 1929)
Vol. 93, no.25 (21 Dec 1929)
Vol. 96, no.4 (24 Jan 1931)
Journal of the American Veterinary Medical Association
Vol. 76/new series Vol. 29, no. 5 (May 1930)
Vol. 78/new series Vol. 31, no. 4 (Apr 1931)
Journal of Bacteriology (the year Moore was an Advisory Editor)
Vol. 3, no. 1 (January 1918)
Vol. 3, no. 2 (March 1918)
Vol. 3, no. 3 (May 1918)
Vol. 3, no. 4 (July 1918)
North American Veterinarian
Vol. 11, no.3 (March 1930)
Vol. 12, no 3 (March 1931)
Science
Vol. 73, no. 1883 (30 Jan 1931)
Vol. 73, no. 1884 (6 Feb 1931)
Vol. 73, no. 1888 (6 March 1931)
Vol. 73, no. 1891 (27 March1931)
Vol. 73, no. 1892 (3 April 1931)
Vol. 73, no. 1899 (22 May 1931)